♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester ♪
♪ And TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an
evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment needed
a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked him
on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him
into space ♪
MIKE: Get me down!
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Now, keep in mind,
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep
his sanity ♪
♪ With the help
of his robot friends ♪
Robot roll call.
-Cambot.
-Show yourself.
-Gypsy.
-Oh, hurry!
-Tom Servo.
-Hello, there.
-Crow.
-That's what I'm...
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
"It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax" ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
[ Doors closing ]
[ Whistles ]
Hi, everyone.
Welcome to the Satellite
of Love.
Hey, Crow.
Check out Mike over here.
-Look at this.
-Hey. Wow.
Mike, what are you doing?
It's cool.
Oh, it's kind of cute.
Well, you know what it is?
It's got a certain--
I don't know.
Elegant simplicity.
Right.
A kind of charm and sweetness
-that...
-That evokes the innocence
-of you?
-Well, yes.
-It's a...
-Whoa. It's alive.
Kill it. Kill it. Kill it.
Kill it. Kill it.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Machine shuts down ]
[ Panting ]
-Tuh.
-Dork.
Weiner.
[ Spits ]
[ Screams ]
Destroy. Destroy.
[ Music playing ]
Mike, what have we learned?
Well, I mean, I think
we've learned that...
You can't build robots.
Say it.
-Say it.
-I can't build robots.
Good.
Now say it a million times.
-Well...
-Hey, a minute.
-Hey.
-The Bobsey Twins are calling.
And don't go building a robot
while you're over there pushing
them button, you moron.
Hello, kids.
It's science project time.
[ Makes sound ]
Fact: In addition
to my huge greatness,
I'm quite a guy.
Everybody likes me.
Now, here we have me,
and here we have a mother.
In this unbiased test,
we shall determine that a robot
trapped in space will choose me
over this not untypical
rather attractive mother.
Now, as I transfer
the science project
via the Umbilicon,
let me explain that Frank,
as the control group,
will be dressed as a pincushion.
This is essential, right?
Absolutely, Frank.
Now, as the control group,
how do you feel?
Well, actually,
in deep physical pain.
That's to be expected.
Well, back to you, Mitchell.
I thought they usually
have two of them.
Okay, fellas,
I guess we got to do this.
Let me handle it,
never did have a mom.
It might be kind of fun.
Okay. Let's see here.
Green.
Soothing color.
Hmm?
Food pouch.
Yummy.
Stitched well.
Should launder fairly easily.
Hmm, soft.
Very soft.
I feel warm,
even secure.
Well, I think
I've made my choice.
I think I'll just take a look
at this one here
before I--
Mommy! Mommy!
-Oh.
-Wow.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Crow.
[ Screams ]
All right. All right.
I can view this coolly,
dispassionately,
it's just that you're so
incredibly stupid and wrong,
you're just so incredibly
stupid and wrong!
Why, I only have to ask
my control group.
Frank?
Who do you prefer?
-Why, you, of course.
-Oh, Frank.
Come here you big-- oh.
FORRESTER: [ Grunts ]
Oh, turn a bit.
Since you dumb dummies
are so stupid and wrong,
I'm going to have to send you
this week's experiment.
It's called "Invasion USA"
preceded by a little
family horror show
called A Date With Your Family.
Push the button, control group.
[ Grunts ]
Whoa, oh,
I got it.
Mommy, mommy.
Crow, Crow,
that's not your mother.
Hmm?
Well, the heck with her.
Are you my mother?
No, you mewling, puking...
-Oh, we got movie sign.
-Come here you...
[ Doors opening ]
CROW: The Woody Allen Story.
MIKE: Hey,
I like my family as a friend.
CROW: All of who are orphans.
MIKE: Now, to our story.
MAN: This boy and girl
coming home from school
look quite content with life.
And why not?
-CROW: They're high.
-MAN: They're looking forward
to an important date,
dinner at home with the family.
SERVO: Sylvia?
MAN: What's the matter?
MIKE:
There's a rabbit in there.
MAN: It doesn't sound
exciting to you?
Well, to them,
it's a special occasion
as it has been ever since
they sat down
to dinner in high chairs.
Why should they feel that way
about something you take
so completely for granted?
-MIKE: Look at them.
-MAN: Well, let's see
if we can find out.
CROW: We secretly switched
their Folgers Coffee...
MAN: First of all,
daughter has changed
from school clothes
to something more festive.
-MIKE: Well, sort of.
-MAN: Dressing a little
makes her feel, and,
consequently look,
more charming.
Even the table takes
on a special air.
MIKE: Ah, and Madame Defarge
waits in the living room.
MAN: Mother, too, chang e s
from her daytime clothes. ..
-CROW: Into Vampira.
-MAN: The women of this family
seem to feel that they owe it
to the men of the family
to look relaxed, rested,
and attractive at dinner time.
MIKE: So they're unsuspecting
when they kill them.
MAN: Brother is spending
an hour before dinner...
-SERVO: Plagiarizing.
-MAN: ...catching up
on his homework.
He has plans this evening.
CROW:
But I won't go into detail.
MAN: Perhaps
that explains the phone call.
But he won't spend a lot of
time on the phone, either.
-MIKE: He's mute.
-MAN: When there are
several members of the family
to be considered,
it is not a good idea
for one member
- to monopolize the phone.
-SERVO: Yeah, double the bet.
MAN: And it is never good to
allow telephone conversation s
to interfere with studies.
CROW:
Even if it's the President.
MIKE: Hi, mom.
I'm pregnant.
MAN: Hmm, is it that late?
Dad will be here any minute.
Better tell mother
she's needed in the kitchen.
SERVO: Where the postman
eagerly awaits.
-MIKE: Sorry.
-CROW: One plus one-- oh.
MAN: Brother notices the time
and realizes that he must
put things in order
and clean himself up
in time for dinner.
MIKE: He's got to strip
and replace the oil in his hair
with summer weight.
SERVO: [ Laughs ]
-MAN: Hello, there.
- SERVO: Who are you?
MAN: Junior is always
in a hurry ,
particularly for dinner.
But, first,
there's a cleanup job to do
on this young man.
CROW: Brother runs a boy
cleaning service on the side.
MAN: Brother takes it
upon himself
to help share
Junior's responsibility
for keeping their room
in good order
and keeping Junior
in good order, too.
MIKE: Brother has a tight
psychological grip on Junior.
MAN: Punctuality is stressed
in this household.
SERVO: Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
MAN:
By that, I mean, hair is combed
and faces and hands scrubbed
before the boys
come to the table
so they won't delay the meal.
MIKE: Come on,
it's time to scrub you.
CROW: Are we all supposed
to be scrubbing each other now?
MAN: Now mother and daughter
put the finishing touches
on the dinner.
SERVO: With strychnine.
CROW:
Salad needs more butter, mother.
-MIKE: A stranger enters.
-MAN: Father, too,
looks forward
to this date with the family.
He has had a hard day
at the office,
and in his briefcase
are some contracts
which must be
looked over tonight.
SERVO:
Okay. Buck up. Here we go.
-MAN: But in the meantime...
-SERVO: Martini.
MAN: ...he will relax
at dinner with those he loves.
CROW: But not these people.
MAN: A simple centerpiece
made from some flowers
-which grow in the backyard...
-MIKE: Is stupid.
MAN: ...is another of daughter's
contributions to the dinner.
But it takes up
a little too much room,
so she moves it
to the sideboard.
CROW:
What you are watching now
should have been edited
in the final version.
My apologies.
SERVO: Come on, come over here.
How much did you earn today?
-Come on, hand it over.
-MAN: ...to meet their dad
as though they are
genuinely glad to see him.
-MIKE: They're not, of course.
-MAN: And so they had really
missed being away from him
during the day,
and they're anxious
to talk to him.
-SERVO: Bob Crane.
-MAN: This is the time
for pleasant discussion
in a thoroughly relaxed mood.
They don't pick this time
of the day
to spring unpleasant surprises
on dad.
If they have disagreeable news,
they will postpone
the discussion
- until another time.
-CROW: When he's asleep.
MAN:
This is no time to dun father
for a raise in your allowance,
new clothes, or argue
about other financial matters.
MIKE:
Father, I had a feeling today.
-SERVO: Well, don't, son.
-MIKE: Okay.
MAN: Ah, dinner time.
Yes, mother, Junior
remembered to clean up.
CROW:
You emasculating bint.
MIKE: Hi, I'm Betty, and I
will be your wife tonight.
SERVO: Well,
this certainly is pleasant.
MAN: Brother seats Junior.
CROW: Daughter
obsesses with the flowers.
MIKE: [ Chuckles ]
MAN: Then helps mother
to her chair
as he would his best girl.
CROW: The less said
about this, the better.
SERVO: Yeah. I got it. I got it.
I got it, honey.
CROW: Junior seats dad
and sister seats the dog,
-and the dog...
-MAN: Well, the dinner date
has begun,
and they're all happy about it.
MIKE: Their stomachs
knotted like fists.
SERVO: Dad, I'm dating a Negro.
MIKE:
Anyone seen our waitress?
MAN: Many families
throughout the country
observe the custom
of saying grace at meal time.
CROW:
Please, God. Take me now.
MAN: It is always treated
with reverence and respect.
SERVO: Field Marshal Montgomery
sits down to eat.
Yes, it's smashing,
it's a good day.
MAN: Napkins on the lap,
the family awaits service.
They converse pleasantly
while dad serves.
MIKE: No, I'll just
have a saltine...
MAN: I said pleasantly
for that is the keynote
at dinnertime.
It is not only good manners
but good sense.
CROW:
Emotions are for ethnic people.
MAN: Pleasant, un-emotional
conversation helps digestion.
SERVO: I can't stress
unemotional enough.
MAN: Father serves mother first,
then daughter.
MIKE: Let's go
to the flowchart for this.
MAN: Then the boys.
Don't worry, fellas,
you won't get left.
CROW: And be sure to make
a plate for the narrator.
SERVO: A violent argument erupts
over whose day
was more pleasant.
CROW:
Can I have chopsticks, please?
MAN:
Help to cut your meat, Junior?
Of course.
SERVO: Ow, ow, ow,
that's my hand.
-Ow.
-MAN: By example,
older children
can teach younger ones
good table manners.
SERVO:
Remember, always cut the meat
of the person to your left.
CROW: You don't have
to cut my mashed potatoes, too,
not the Jell-O.
MAN: And no one starts eating
until father has
served himself.
-CROW: This means you.
-MAN: Always wait
for the hostess,
in this case, mother,
to begin eating
before you start.
MIKE: Father feigns eating,
draws Junior out,
-then disowns him.
-MAN: Let father and mother
guide the conversational
trend if they desire.
After all, they made
all this possible,
and they want to talk
over their day with each other.
CROW:
I'm moving to Fire Island, dear.
MAN: Tell mother
how good the food is.
MIKE: Even as you gag on it.
MAN: ... a compliment, too.
-MIKE: This stinks.
-MAN: It makes them want
to continue pleasing you.
CROW: After all,
that's why God put women
on this green Earth.
MAN: Well, all of this
is good general advice,
but there are
some specific don'ts.
Maybe the family
will demonstrate for us.
Don't monopolize
the conversation
and go on and on
without stopping.
-MIKE: God.
-MAN: Nothing destroys
the charm of a meal
more quickly.
MIKE: Than having a personality.
MAN: To say that the rest
of the group is bored
would be a gross
understatement.
SERVO: Mother, do something.
CROW: At least I have two sons.
MAN:
Don't discuss unpleasant topics
such as gruesome sights
or sounds...
SERVO: So then sister
made Patrick get him up...
MAN:
...or unpleasant occurrences.
This is a time of pleasure,
of charm, and relaxation,
remember?
MIKE: I have no son.
MAN:
Don't make unkind comparisons
about your stand of living.
The dinner table is no place
for discontent.
It makes dad and mother
uncomfortable and unhappy.
CROW: And they already
dislike you enough.
SERVO: Mm-hmm.
Well, there it is, spankings
all around, then.
Oh, and she was a big nun
with a mustache,
-this huge black...
-MAN: Don't insult your brother
or sister with offensive
remarks about friends.
Arguments, harsh words,
mean tension,
and distress for everyone.
SERVO: Yeah, go piss up a rope.
CROW:
Sit and spin you cruddy skank.
SERVO: Perhaps booze
would alleviate this situation.
MAN: Do remember simply this,
treat the other members
of your family
with the same respect
and cordiality
you would show your most
treasured friend
outside the family circle.
-SERVO: So snap dad's bra?
-MAN: This does not mean
you should be stiff or formal.
With your own family,
you can relax.
Be yourself.
Just be sure
it's your best self.
CROW: And be sure
no one knows the real you.
MAN: This is better.
SERVO: Father
does his ferret impression.
MAN: Now all things
are on an even keel again.
MIKE: And everyone wants to flee
the seething cauldron of angst.
MAN:
Now we're ready for dessert.
Most families don't have maids.
-CROW: They have daughters.
-MAN: So mother needs help
with the serving
from the kitchen.
Son says mother
has done enough.
Watch him play butler.
SERVO: In "Remains of the Day."
MAN: The removal of dishes
from the main course
and the serving of dessert
set the stage
for the conclusion
of a thoroughly pleasant meal.
SERVO: I probably should've
washed my hands
after handling that dead
woodchuck, oh, well.
-You want gin, pop?
-No.
MAN: Do you begin to see now
how a date with your family
can be a truly
special occasion?
-SERVO: Do you? Do you?
-MAN: Why brother and sister
looked forward to the evening?
SERVO: Well, do you?
Better say yes, damn it!
MAN:
When the dinner hour at home
is treated with a certain
amount of graciousness
and ceremony,
it can be memorable.
There is not family so poor,
but that the evening meal
can be eaten
in an atmosphere
of warmth and gentleness.
SERVO: And control
and repression.
MAN: There is no family so busy,
but that it can come together
in the evening
for a dinner date,
which will give its members
something to look back upon
with happiness
all their days.
CROW: You know,
this makes me wanna heat up
a Libbyland dinner
and eat in front of the TV.
-MIKE: Mm-hmm.
-SERVO: Now, enjoy
some refreshments in the lobby.
MIKE: I'll buy.
CROW: A Simmel-Meservey release.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: Invasion USA?
CROW: Wow.
MIKE: Starring these people
and Chuck Norris.
CROW: Ooh.
SERVO: And the entire
Gotham City council.
MIKE: Let's see, Phyllis Coates,
hey, there's two Lois Lanes
in this movie, at least.
CROW: Yeah.
SERVO: What do you know?
What? And the lead singer of
The Cure is a screenwriter, too.
I had no idea.
CROW: [ Makes sound ]
With Albert Glasser conducting
the Invasion USA orchestra.
[ Imitates trumpet ]
SERVO: Relentless.
This music is like
a good Danny Elfman tune.
CROW: You mean it doesn't exist?
SERVO: Boom.
MIKE: Hey, you know,
I think I had an apartment
-in this building over here.
-SERVO: Yeah?
Oh, did you now?
-Cold water flat...
-CROW: Looks like
James Sullivan really had
his work cut out for him.
-MIKE: Cut out.
-CROW: Oh, stop it.
SERVO: Yeah.
MIKE: Let's get on
with it here, please.
SERVO: Please, yeah.
Ah, the Zugsmith touch,
dry but warm.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: What? Me direct?
MIKE: Ah, bustling city music.
SERVO: Of course.
Thinville,
the thinnest city in the world.
CROW: Why does my back hurt?
Must be lifting
this thing wrong.
MIKE:
Oh, thank heavens, civilization.
SERVO: ♪ Cucaracha,
la cucaracha ♪
-[ Speaking Spanish ]
-Ladies and gentlemen,
I'll have a complete sports
roundup for you
in just a moment.
CROW: That guy's just
sitting in the next room.
MAN: Another bourbon.
Coming right up.
MIKE:
Shouldn't he be guarding Oswald?
SERVO:
Ah, breakfast at Harry's bar,
cornflakes with gin.
Here's the news bulletin
from The Nation's Capital.
Washington officially
this morning denies rumors
of enemy planes
over northern Alaska.
Meanwhile,
there has been no lessening
of international tension
and informed sources
refuse to discount
the possibility of all-out war.
MIKE: Yeah, David Byrne.
I got enough war talk at home.
You can say that again.
Meanwhile in Italy,
the communists caused another...
Quiet, Jay.
- ...as communist march on...
-SERVO: That's nice.
That'll hold you.
MIKE: I'm still here barkeep.
I wish I could keep him
that quiet
when he comes in here.
-Customer of yours?
-Yeah.
The TV station's
right down the street.
CROW:
He's a chainsaw sculpture.
And what do you think
the lug drinks?
MAN: A sherry flip.
Oh, you must know him, huh?
MIKE: Excuse me, I'm right
in the middle of Slow Waltz
in Cedar Bend.
-You've seen him in here?
-No.
MAN: Well, then,
how did you know...?
He looks like the sort of person
who'd drink a sherry flip.
Say, he does at that!
SERVO: I don't get it.
-MIKE: Kramer.
-SERVO: Hey.
All right, Tim,
how about a beer?
SERVO: You can
all admire me now.
-MAN: Is you workin' today?
-Yeah, but I thought
I'd work in a nice, cool bar.
SERVO:
And pound drink after drink.
...you, sir?
My name is Potter, Vince Potter.
I'm a commentator for
station TVNY.
Would you mind answering
a question
-for tomorrow's program?
-SERVO: The Beatles.
You're gonna use it
on television?
-CROW: Pilgrim.
-That's the idea.
Well, gosh, I'll be glad to.
Good. First, I'll get your name
and address, huh?
Ed Mulberry.
Boulder County, Arizona.
-Arizona?
-SERVO: I came here
-to be a gigolo.
-I'm a cattle raiser.
Cattle raiser?
MIKE: Races cattle, okay.
Now, here's today's question.
Are you for or against
the universal draft?
Now, by that I mean,
draft everything.
Soldiers for the army,
factories for war work,
labor for factories,
the whole business.
-Well...
-CROW: My puzzler hurts.
...government
in business already.
-You take cattle now.
-SERVO: Mm-hmm.
One bureau shoves the cost
of feed up
and another keeps the price
of beef down.
That's why I cut my herd
down to 3,000 head this year.
SERVO: It's great,
but it's not the question.
I would raise 5,000
if they hadn't put
price controls on.
-Another bourbon.
-CROW: Make it a quadruple.
And they soak you with those
income taxes, oh, brother.
CROW: Scanners.
You pay a high income tax?
Plenty.
You must make
a great deal of money.
I do all right.
MIKE: Make more than you,
you fruit.
Down with taxes.
SERVO: Pass the beer nuts,
you back ass cracker.
MIKE: The conversation
takes an abrupt shift.
SERVO: I don't stand
a chance, do I?
What would you like, honey?
A scotch over ice.
I don't know why you
New Yorkers drink scotch.
Stuff tastes
like medicine to me.
What do you drink
in San Francisco?
-Daiquiri.
-MIKE: Hmm, nice.
That sounds
like a sissy drink to me.
I just like the cracked ice.
Scotch on a cracked ice.
CROW: [ Makes sound ]
VINCE: I beg your pardon.
-I'm Vince Potter.
-Yeah?
At television station TVNY.
Oh, yes.
I'd like to ask you
both a question.
But, first, may I have
your name, sir?
Sylvester. George Sylvester.
Your occupation?
I'm a tractor manufacturer.
CROW: A daiquiri swilling
tractor manufacturer, okay.
-Your name.
-SERVO: The worst.
CROW: And your breasts?
Uh, I mean occupation?
-[ Indistinct ]
-Telephone number?
1717...
-Now, look here...
-It's all right, George.
I listen to Mr. Potter
every Friday.
His program is very popular
in New York.
So is he, evidently.
Thank you.
Now, here's tonight's question,
Mr. Sylvester.
Are you for or against
the universal draft,
army, labor,
factory, everything?
SERVO: Oh, lights out,
everybody drink up.
-...communism?
-Communism?
That's a good quote.
They tried that
on me last week.
But I told 'em where to get off.
Last week? Where was that?
-My plant.
-SERVO: In Moscow.
They sent an army major in
to see me.
It would take me six months
to get in production
on these tank parts.
In the meantime, what would
happen to my tractors, sir?
The army needs tanks,
Mr. Sylvester.
Oh, sure.
I'd like to hear you tell that
to some of my dealers.
If your dealers
are good Americans,
they'll know that tanks are
more important than tractors.
All they know is they don't
get tractors to sell,
they're out of business.
If an enemy nation
conquered America,
they'd be out of business
for good.
Fat chance.
SERVO: Now go on,
punch me hard.
I'm sorry, major, I'd like
to accommodate you,
but I've spent 10 years
in building up
my sales organization,
and I'm not going
to throw it away
to do the government a favor.
Mr. Sylvester, if people
like you won't cooperate
with your government willingly,
the day may come when we'll be
forced to take over your plants
without asking
your permission.
-SERVO: Believe that.
-Over my dead body.
Now, let me tell you something,
major.
-SERVO: Uh-oh. No.
-The people in this country
-will never stand...
-SERVO: Stop it. No.
...so you can go back to
Washington and tell them that.
SERVO: I wanna go.
Leave me alone.
Yes, sir. Just because he was
wearing a major's uniform,
he thought
he could threaten me.
-But I sure told him...
-SERVO: Tom Waits, hey.
Well, your girlfriend
and I got to go.
-MIKE: What?
-Do you believe in drafting
women as well as men?
Well, it all depends
on what you wanna draft us for.
CROW:
Whoa, got a live one here.
I mean, labor in a munitions
factory, for instance.
I worked in a factory
for a while during the last war.
-SERVO: Naked.
-They'd ruined my hands,
so I quit.
Another drink, Tim,
for everybody.
SERVO: Oh, Foster Brooks
joins in.
...young lady,
Haraway's my name.
Congressman Haraway.
I'm just in New York
for over the weekend.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Well, it's nice to know you,
too.
-MIKE: Whatever.
-Valuable work
you're doing, young man,
seeking the voice
of the people.
I believe it, and
that's the American way,
-the democratic way.
-Thank you, sir. That's...
MIKE:
This is starting to bang, huh?
CROW: Will somebody
please invade something?
You won't mention the locale
of our interview, of course.
[ Doors closing ]
SERVO: Michael, I must say
that you have prepared
these victuals
with much regalement.
-Indeed.
-Well, thank you, Thomas,
and while we partake
of these aromatic comestibles,
there's no reason
why we cannot converse
in a refined
and dignified manner.
-Ah, yes.
-Indeed.
Say, how about
that sporting event, hmm?
One team emerged the victor,
whereas the other, alas,
found themselves vanquished.
Ah, but such are the
vicissitudes of sport.
Hmm. Indeed.
You know,
the other day,
I had the occasion
to witness a cultural event.
It seemed to point
to the foibles
of everyday living.
Afterwards, I reflected
upon the stimulating nature
-of the presentation.
-Mm-hmm.
Recently, I was taken
by a particular article
of literature.
The author used sentences
and paragraphs
to express his point of view.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, that reminds me
of a pleasantry
I was exposed to recently.
An anecdote happened
that might be interpreted
as whimsical.
It provided all parties involved
with a puckish sense
of diverting amusement.
[ Laughter ]
Mike, this sucks.
Can we just eat?
-Oh, yeah.
-That's a great--
...they're all dead.
I'm making...
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Music playing ]
Maybe I'd better get you in...
May I have your name, sir?
My name is Ohman.
-Ohman?
-SERVO: Yes. But my friends
-call me Shotsie.
-...like a band leader,
O-H-M-A-N, isn't it?
SERVO:
Yeah, I get that all the time.
And your occupation, Mr. Ohman?
-SERVO: Communist, I mean...
-I'm a forecaster.
Weather forecaster.
Now, what do you think
of the draft?
I think America wants
new leadership.
-New leadership?
-SERVO: Ja.
What kind of leadership
do you suggest?
-CROW: Puppies.
-I suggest a wizard.
-A what?
-A wizard like Merlin,
who could kill his enemies
by wishing them dead.
MIKE: Poof.
That's the way we like
to beat communism now
by wishing it dead.
SERVO: He's dreamy.
-He's dreamy.
-OHMAN: ...and lower taxes,
labor wants more consumer
products in a 30-hour week.
A college boy wants
a stronger army.
-SERVO: He does?
-And a deferment for himself.
The businessman wants
a bigger air force
and a new Cadillac.
-SERVO: He does?
-The housewife wants security
and an electric dishwasher.
CROW:
I just want a working nose.
Everybody wants
a strong America,
and we all want
the same man to pay for it.
SERVO: Ross Perot.
George.
Let George do it.
Ah, ah, I disagree with you.
I don't wanna let George do it.
You must be the exception?
No. I'm George.
[ Laughter ]
SERVO: I like you.
I'll kill you last.
Everyone wants George to do it.
Except George.
SERVO:
I think I just said that joke.
A very good joke,
but wars are not won
by making jokes.
SERVO: Ah, every party
needs a pooper.
-To win a war...
-SERVO: You need brandy.
-Lots of it.
-...a nation must concentrate.
SERVO: I could use a man like
you in my organization. Norm!
-CROW: Norm!
-SERVO: Norm!
MIKE: Must go home
and kill parents.
SERVO: Plenty of scotch.
Very nice legs, yes.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Oh, that reminds me,
I have to clean the toilet bowl.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: What's that say?
Mastery not victory?
CROW: Castro's an okay guy.
CROW: Dalton Trumbo's
a good screenwriter.
CROW: Roy Cohn
is our greatest obstacle,
I wonder if there are
any beer nuts left.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: Mentiary.
SERVO: Hey turn it up,
Max Headroom's on.
CROW: Excuse me,
I have to go
to the little ubermensch's room.
Something big going on.
Speak up, jerk.
No longer a rumor,
the blue alert is on...
SERVO: Nation gripped
by aches and pains.
Here's the news bulletin
from United Press,
a wireless operator
from Seal Point, Alaska
reports over 500 planes
were seen
at 4:20 this afternoon.
Five hundred planes?
What kind of planes?
MAN: They passed over
Seal Point at an altitude
of 10,000 feet, heading south.
SERVO: Isn't that kind
of a Garth Brooks shirt on?
CROW: Something
about Armageddon, sir.
A dispatch from Washington:
All military leaves
are canceled,
members of the armed forces
are to report
to the nearest headquarters
immediately.
SERVO: All public
and parochial schools...
Good-bye.
MIKE: Aren't these wars phony?
MAN: Nome, Alaska
more than 50 reports
from all over the territory
have now been received
hundreds of unidentified
aircraft are unquestionably
moving south across Alaska.
The latest report comes from
the seaport of Peace Harbor.
MIKE: Huh, ironic.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Should we splash
on Old Spice, sir?
CROW: Quack, quack, quack.
SERVO: Quack, quack.
CROW: Boss, the plane,
the plane.
MIKE: Oh, don't.
CROW: I'm really sorry.
MIKE: It's the first
Russian doo-wop group.
MAN: Attention,
all civilian air personnel,
report any observations
on the identity
of the approaching planes,
to the Alaskan
high command immediately.
-SERVO: Okay.
-MAN: I repeat.
MAN: Here they come.
MAN: Attention,
all civilian air personnel,
report any observations
on the identity
- of the approaching planes...
-MIKE: You just said that.
...the Alaskan
high command immediately.
-Can you see their markings?
-Not yet.
SERVO: Watch your backside,
Maverick.
♪ Highway to the
Danger Zone... ♪
[ Makes sound ]
They're coming at us.
CROW: I think
they're enemy planes, sir.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Ah, plane poop,
the worst kind.
MIKE: There goes the luggage.
-That's what happens
-CROW: 100-piece
-action figure.
-MIKE: You know this is
how my mom dropped me
off at school every day.
-CROW: No.
-MIKE: Yes.
SERVO: For some reason
I can't help but think
Bobbie Gentry
had something to do with this.
I don't know.
-MIKE: I don't know, either.
-Hold that flag down.
MIKE: I'll do everything,
you guys just stand there.
CROW: Not exactly Iwo Jima.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: The Spruce Goose.
Peace Harbor calling Nome,
Peace Harbor calling Nome.
SERVO: Can I take my break
early please?
The enemy...
[ Gunshots ]
...is here.
CROW: More later.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: [ Makes sound ]
MAN: Hurry those bombs.
The Racine JCs
prepare another
fireworks display.
MIKE: War, huh,
what is it good for?
CROW: Absolutely nothing.
SERVO: Say it again.
MIKE: War, good God, y'all.
What is it good for?
CROW: Absolutely nothing.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Well, let's see here,
okay, let's pin it on there,
oh, wait, no that's wrong.
SERVO: Entering
the courtroom are litigants.
CROW: The most feared
geography teacher
-of Central High.
-SERVO: Wow.
Here's our headquarters.
Here is the target
for group A for Atlas.
MIKE: What?
B for Berlin.
SERVO: T for Texas.
C for Canada,
D for Dover.
SERVO: Will we have any
free time during the fall, sir?
CROW: Wow, they need
their emissions checked.
SERVO: [ Coughs ]
MIKE: Should really think
about ride sharing for the war.
SERVO: ♪ They're leaving ♪
♪ On some jet planes ♪
-MIKE: That was too cool.
-This is Marx Manning again,
ladies and gentlemen,
unconfirmed reports state
that our jet fighter planes
have already engaged the enemy.
SERVO: See, look.
MARX: From the United Press
correspondent
in Fairbanks, Alaska,
it's now certain
that the United States
has been attacked
without warning.
Three civil airports in Alaska
have been captured,
a dozen more don't reply
to urgent radio calls,
there's a great deal of static
in the northwest
probably due to enemy
jamming of the air waves.
The big mystery now
is why have no cities
been attacked,
why did the enemy
throw away surprise,
yet failed to drop
a single atom bomb?
CROW: It's long par-5
leading up
to the nation's capital.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: It was supposed to be
four sides, but the military
screwed it up.
Civilian airfields in Alaska,
why?
He must plan to use them
for staging an attack
on our factories,
our cities, our shipyards,
and our airfields.
CROW: Eight ball corner pocket.
He's made several attacks
on the Pacific fleet.
It was completely wiped out.
G2 reports
that the attacking forces
are wearing American uniforms.
-Wow.
-MIKE: They don't have
the figures
for American uniforms.
The question now,
is he going to use his A bomb?
SERVO: Because if he is,
I'm not.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Here they come.
-MIKE: Hey, look...
-Bombs away.
MIKE: ...his helmet
is ribbed for her pleasure.
SERVO: Wow.
Boy, I feel great.
Nothing could spoil--
[ Servo groaning ]
CROW: Well, that's what happens
when you overcook a brat
in a microwave.
SERVO: Ah, sorry, duck's off.
CROW: ♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Do-do-do ♪
Well, hmm.
Nobody can drop just one.
Once you get it in your system,
you want it every night.
SERVO: That's the same airfield.
They rebuilt it already.
They're like cockroaches.
MAN: Bombs away.
MIKE: He's a very strange man.
Did you invite him?
CROW: Hey, everybody
it's a beautiful day.
Ah!
SERVO: Bomb's so nice,
he dropped it twice.
CROW:
We have got to move this base.
This keeps happening.
Look, a president.
MIKE: Kind of spooky, actually.
SERVO: Kind of like
watching a Yule Log.
So, ladies and gentlemen,
the long-awaited...
SERVO: What's going
on in sports? Come on.
The atom bomb has been dropped
on the United States
of America.
CROW: Oh, wait. It hasn't.
Washington, 10:30 p.m.,
the Joint Chiefs of Staff
are now in session.
So far, there have been
official reports
of only three A-bomb drops.
CROW: Hey, that's not so bad.
...but unofficial information
is to the effect
that additional
military objectives
have been hit in the northwest
and on the Pacific coast.
The bombs used are reported
to be nearly as strong...
...as the American bomb
dropped on Nagasaki.
SERVO: Hey, cut it out over
there.
We now interrupt
this news summary
to take you to Washington, D.C.
SERVO: You've heard
of Washington, D.C.?
And so, another day of infamy
has come
within your lifetime and mine.
CROW: Uh, sir, we're over here.
Thousands of Americans
have died,
victims of this
treacherous attack.
SERVO: Well, c'est la vie .
But it will not go unpunished.
MIKE: Barkeep,
can I post-date this check?
...hundreds
of our fastest bombers
are speeding toward
the enemy's homeland.
SERVO:
At an incredibly low altitude.
MAN: We shall bomb their bases,
and their army,
their factories,
and their railroads.
-SERVO: Their distilleries.
-MAN: Their harbors
and their oil fields.
SERVO: Their toaster factory,
where you get the...
MAN: Our own atom bomb,
more powerful
than any the world
has ever known,
would wreck
a terrible vengeance
upon that nation
whose long threat
to the peace of the world.
SERVO: It's under a big W.
MAN: Today became a reality.
CROW: Oh, shoot this is Canada.
-MIKE: Oh.
-CROW: Bomb anyways.
MIKE: Mailbox Of Values
pulls out all the stops.
SERVO:
Nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya.
MIKE: The president stated,
"I'm rubber, you're glue.
Everything you bomb
bounces back to you."
CROW:
They're bombing Moorhead State.
SERVO: Oh, boy.
Ah, oh that feels good.
-Ah, yeah, ugh.
-CROW: Stop that, Serv.
You can carpet bomb
in the afternoon
and entertain guests at night.
Hey, more peanuts up here.
Why, they're practically
giving these things away.
[ Explosion ]
CROW: They're dropping
little liver pills.
SERVO: If-- you know,
if I had one of these planes,
I'd go to my house,
put the bombs in my garage,
and watch Love Connection,
then I'd just tell everybody
I dropped them.
That would be better,
wouldn't it?
MIKE: Oh, fun is fun,
but let's get back to the base.
MAN: And while our bombers
are carrying the war
to the enemy's homeland...
-CROW: Are you still here?
-MAN: American fighter planes
and the air arm of our fleet
are valiantly
defending the shores
of our Pacific coast.
CROW: Hold on here.
Hello, you're on K-WAR.
Pilots man your planes.
SERVO:
And let's be careful out there.
CROW: As your president,
let me just apologize
for not having seen
this invasion coming.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Come on, vogue.
SERVO: Wait, come back,
he didn't mean it!
[ Music playing ]
CROW: He's safe!
MIKE: Out of the way.
SERVO:
Attention, Operation Petticoat
will not be seen tonight
because it's not very good.
CROW: Surrender, Dorothy.
[ Music playing ]
-CROW: Well...
-SERVO: Hmm.
CROW: You know, this...
Where's the enemy?
Look at those swept back wings.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: This was all
cut from Free Willy.
SERVO: Yeah, this sucks.
I'm knocking off for lunch.
CROW: Yeah, me, too.
MIKE: Yeah,
I suppose I'll go with you.
CROW: Look, I just wanna be
with myself tonight.
MAN: Strike their carrier.
MIKE: Why is there a dogfight
in the middle of a nuclear war?
CROW: I got it,
under control, I'm okay.
I think I'm pulling it up now.
SERVO: They mugged
David L. Wolper or something?
[ Explosion ]
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: Would you guys
quit fooling around up there?
CROW: Thirty hours over Tokyo.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: See, air traffic
controllers go on strike,
and this is the result here.
CROW: I've heard of
fear wars... but come on.
[ Music playing ]
CROW:
Hey, is something burning?
Would you look in back there?
Yes, dozens
of stunt fliers
were killed
during the making of this film.
MIKE: I swear I smell something.
It's probably okay, but-- ooh.
Now I call upon
all Americans...
CROW: To reject stock footage.
...to join ranks
in this bitter struggle
with the forces of evil.
-SERVO: Hmm.
-Forces that will never rest
until they have
conquered the Earth.
CROW:
Big Brother's kind of shy.
Or are themselves conquered
by the united strength...
-SERVO: Of America.
-...of the free peoples
-of the world.
-SERVO: Oh.
CROW: This is
the worst happy hour ever.
Turn it off.
CROW: Flash,
Pearl Harbor has just been.
Where's the congressman?
He left for Washington
a couple of hours ago.
How about that Phil Ohman?
He's gone, too.
Can you imagine those guys
attacking the United States
of America?
-SERVO: Pilgrim...
-Yeah, well, we'll shove it
down their throats.
This is it,
the final game
of the World Series,
and we're the home team.
-SERVO: And we're the Mariners.
-Give me a beer, Tim,
while I got some voice left,
will you?
-CROW: A newsman who drinks?
-MAN: Hi.
-CARLA: Hi.
-SERVO: No.
-Is it as bad as it sounds?
-Worse.
What's the inside joke,
friends?
-MIKE: Oh, my queue rating...
-Oh, we lost part of the State
of Washington,
about 50 military airfields
in the west.
-SERVO: Bits of Texas.
-Knocked out by atom bombs.
It was like a modern
kamikaze attack.
No matter how many planes
we shot down,
they kept coming
until one got through.
CROW: Man, it was cool.
...was operating from carriers
off the coast of Oregon.
They've taken a horrific toll
of enemy planes.
SERVO:
I'm turning in to Dick York.
How about
the cities in California?
-You mean San Francisco?
-Yeah.
-It hasn't been attacked yet.
-SERVO: World War III separates
the serious drinkers
from the amateurs.
But they hit a shipyard
in the state of Washington,
20,000 dead.
-Oh, no.
-Oh, yes.
But what are they up to?
I mean, they wouldn't just
drop a few bombs
and let it go at that.
There was a rumor that they
were dropping parachute troops
near Puget Sound.
In American uniforms.
CROW: It's the end of the world.
Turn it on again, will you, Tim?
We were trying to pick up
the Tacoma station
by microwave when I left.
-MIKE: We can do that?
-Do you think there will be
an actual invasion?
I wish I knew.
CROW:
Hmm, that goes down smooth.
-Hard to believe it, but...
-SERVO: Mm-hmm.
-MIKE: I knew.
-I mean, that this is actually
happening to us.
[ Music playing ]
Hey, porcupine,
wanna watch me
make Crow look like an idiot?
No.
But if you're going to, anyway.
Hey, Crow.
You rang?
Uh, Crow, I'm having
a terrible time deciding
which Lois Lane from Superman
I like better...
-Noel Neill or Phyllis Coates.
-Ahh.
Well, firstly, Servo,
it's The Adventures of Superman.
-Ah, of course.
-Secondly, you're not the first
to grapple with that question.
There are no easy answers.
-Well, the-- hey, may I?
-Oh, sure.
Hey, Crow, which Lois Lane
do you prefer?
Well, permit me to put
the Phyllis Coates-Noel Neill
debate in context, Michael.
Noel Neill played Lois Lane
in the radio serials
in the '40s,
so, naturally, one would think
she was the clear choice
to be Lois Lane
in the television series
in 1951.
Sure, yeah.
Yes, any layman
might think that.
Actually, it was Phyllis Coates
who played Lois Lane
in the first year of the series.
Then, Phyllis Coates was ousted,
and Noel Neill returned
to the role she had originated.
Wow, interesting.
More than interesting, Mike,
spooky.
-Oh.
-But I leave
the conspiracy theories
to Oliver Stone.
[ Laughing ]
Gee, Crow,
how were Phyllis Coates
and Noel Neill different?
Good question,
very good question.
Oh, thank you.
You were at
my Frankfurt lecture series, no?
Never mind.
Let's compare and contrast
Phyllis Coates and Noel Neill.
Michael, the chart, please?
Oh, right. Okay. Sure.
-Chart, yes.
-You see, this chart
clearly illustrates
that Lois Lane
as played by Phyllis Coates
was a tough,
hard-nosed reporter.
Ah, and Lois Lane
as played by Noel Neill
was sensitive and caring.
Well, let's not get into that
whole Kirk/Picard thing here.
They were both very good.
So, which one played
Juan Epstein?
Well, that's
a very interesting question
because you see-- hey,
you just made me look
like a complete idiot.
-You're welcome.
-Thank you.
-Hey. Don't...
-We got movie sign.
CROW:
Oh, I'm dying. I'm dying.
[ Doors opening ]
MAN: Here's another
remote-controlled view
from our portable equipment.
Here are regular
American troops.
CROW: And here are new,
improved American troops.
MAN: ...St. Louis, hiding
with the invading paratroopers.
MIKE: Should we kiss, honey?
I think we should kiss.
SERVO: I'm a simple cameraman.
MAN: Ever taken
of American soldiers .
-CROW: Oh. Aw. whoa.
-MAN: . ..on American so il.
SERVO: Ow.
MIKE: What color is
your parachute?
MAN: Here's the target,
enemy paratroopers crashing
at a field near Puget Sound.
CROW: Oh, God,
that hurts, oh, oh, oh.
MAN:
We are taking these pictures
from station
TVWN's portable cameras,
equipped with telescopic lens.
But even so, our mobile unit
is within a quarter of a mile
of the actual battle.
MIKE:
Ah, completely successful, oh.
MAN: There goes one.
MIKE: You smell like
breeding stock.
MAN: But it will take more
than a handful of riflemen
to hold back the thousands
of well-equipped troops
who are dropping
out of the skies above us here
in the State of Washington.
MIKE: Wow.
CROW: Ooh.
MAN: We're having trouble
with our picture.
I hope our microwave
is getting through to the east.
- We want all Americans to...
-CROW: Try switching to radar.
-Well...
-Ladies and gentlemen,
our connection with Tacoma
has been broken.
We will restore it
if and when we can.
-SERVO: We certainly will.
-Meanwhile...
here's the official
confirmation
of an earlier rumor.
Washington, D.C.,
the Department of Defense
announces that
the Pacific Shipyards
have been destroyed
by atom bombing.
The same bomb smashed the
business district of the city
with casualties
estimated between 20...
CROW: Nobody wants
to mention his lisp.
MIKE: No.
I guess I'd better
get back to San Francisco.
Do you think it's safe?
It's my town.
You're gonna try
for an airplane ticket?
It's what I had in mind.
I think I'll go along with you.
-CROW: Oh, good.
-...Arizona.
When I get back home, I'll tell
Edna that I'm not likely
to forget my dinner date
with her cousin.
MIKE: That guy's Big Boy.
You go find your plane ticket.
I'm not hungry, anyway.
You see
that she gets home safe.
I'll make it
my personal responsibility.
-SERVO: Uh-huh.
-Good-bye, then.
Take care of yourself, George.
Good luck.
SERVO: I'd like to invade you,
if you don't mind.
MAN: This is
an emergency announcement.
This is
Every able-bodied citizen
is requested to report
to the nearest hospital to
give blood for the Red Cross.
SERVO: In-va-va-va-va-vasion.
[ Shuddering ]
It can't be happening.
It was a cinch to happen.
MIKE: Oh, you're here?
Last time I met a girl
I really liked,
they bombed Pearl Harbor.
-CROW: I thought it was...
-What happened to the girl?
War ended.
MAN:
♪ Extra paper, America invaded ♪
♪ Read all about it ♪
♪ Extra paper ♪
♪ America invaded ♪
♪ Read all about it ♪
-MIKE: Oh, that's a walk-on.
-SERVO: Yeah.
Please, let me through.
I'm a Texan.
WOMAN: Okay. Thanks.
Sorry, nothing for New Orleans.
-SERVO: Hey. Ooh.
-Anything from Minneapolis?
-Nothing for Minneapolis.
-MAN: Anything for Omaha?
All flights for Omaha
are sold out, sir.
-Well, how about tomorrow?
-Tomorrow? No.
-Next week.
-SERVO: Lois Lane got a fro.
I hope you can help me.
My wife is very ill in Dallas.
I can get you a reservation
a week from next Tuesday,
but you have to get a priority.
Here's where you apply
for it, sir.
CROW:
Oh, Noel Neill, Lois number two.
WOMAN: ...for Gardiner Field,
Montana.
-Gardiner Field, Montana?
-SERVO: "Can you give me
a ticket-- Gardiner Field?"
-Get out of here.
-Is this a business trip?
No, I wanna go home.
My husband's there,
and my children.
They're with him.
SERVO: I'll save you the time,
they're all dead.
...all flights to Gardiner Field
have been discontinued.
-Discontinued?
-SERVO: Mm-hmm.
For how long?
-I'm afraid permanently.
-CROW: Ten thousand years.
There hadn't been an attack.
Early this morning.
SERVO: What a stressful airline.
An A-bomb.
MIKE: Hey, look, they're dead.
Let's move it along, lady.
CROW:
The hat squad consoles her.
SERVO: So, what are you doing
later on, little lady?
Are you busy or...?
I don't think we'll do
any good here.
You know,
there's a bellhop in my hotel,
you know, with all the angles.
SERVO: Calls himself Euclid.
-You're right.
-CROW: Ma'am, we need hookers.
Anything to get to Phoenix
or Tucson?
All sold out.
How about San Francisco?
Still a few spaces left,
if you can get a priority.
SERVO: Anything left
for Uriah Heep?
-...here.
-Thanks.
You know, I think I'll try
for San Francisco with you.
Maybe I can rent a car there
and drive home.
Fine, come along.
I'd like a ticket to Seattle.
SERVO: Look, they're dead.
And when you pledge
to the Soviet Union,
you get this nifty
tote bag and...
Are you sure you understood
my instructions?
SERVO: Idaho, damn it,
show me Idaho.
We have lost aircraft 8 and 9,
and there are still two
fields remaining.
-SERVO: Filter fields.
-Here and here.
CROW:
Now, show me West Virginia.
Regardless of loss,
let's concentrate
two aircrafts on each one.
[ Indistinct ]
with our own bomb.
MIKE: [ Indistinct ]
bury the bombs?
And then order the attack
on San Francisco
praising the ready stage.
Immediately, Excellency.
MIKE: Now,
will the dancing Hitlers,
please get to this side.
SERVO: We got a real pretty view
of the dust cloud
out the right window.
It's currently 7,000 degrees
in San Francisco.
MAN: New York, Flight 289,
to San Francisco tower,
request landing instructions.
SERVO: Well, just keep
coming down
until you're not
in the sky anymore.
Don't you know how to land?
-Over.
-Tower to TWA Flight 289,
land on strip three.
CROW: Hey, look,
there's Tony Bennett's heart.
SERVO: They're
on Armageddon location
in beautiful San Francisco.
MIKE: If we're real quiet,
maybe, he won't look up.
SERVO: Shh.
CROW: Oh, let's go straight
to the wharf.
MIKE: Oh, Ghirardelli Square.
SERVO: Oh, PIER 39, please.
CROW: I really am a cowboy.
We're not gay.
MAN: This is KRO San Francisco.
While no A bombs
have fallen on California,
an unofficial report
from Northern California
states that six ships
flying the flags
of six different nations
were intercepted
by the United States Navy
and found to be carrying enemy
personnel and equipment.
Turn it off, will you, mac?
Anything you say.
SERVO: Let's just talk.
The Golden Gate,
there is San Francisco.
SERVO: Ja,
it's home of Rice-A-Roni.
MIKE: Ja.
CROW: Well, it looks like
San Francisco is about to be
sautéed and simmered.
SERVO: Hey, you know what?
They're probably going to bomb
-the Grateful Dead.
-MIKE: Yeah, go, go, go.
-CROW: And Starship, whoo.
-SERVO: Yeah, whoo.
Open fire.
[ Cannon fire ]
CROW: Go away, you
poopy-caca-head Russians.
[ Cannon fire continues ]
SERVO: I mean, I'm from Texas,
that's why I dress this way.
-I'm not gay.
-What's that?
MIKE: It's the end of the world
as we know it, and I feel fine.
It's a B-29.
CROW: Why is Knute Rockne,
All-American,
piloting the plane?
There is the target.
SERVO: Good, I got to pick up
some light bulbs.
I love that one.
CROW: Mantis.
MAN: Bombs away.
CROW: Help the bombardier.
SERVO: You know,
they'll bomb Bobby McFerrin,
and Robin Williams.
-Hurray!
-MIKE: Yes.
[ Cannon fire ]
Servo: B-29.
MIKE: Well, we got them,
might as well use them.
[ Bombs whistling,
explosions ]
-CROW: Hey, you see all kinds.
-Up ahead, pull up to the curb.
CROW: I can't stop.
I can't stop.
[ Cannon fire ]
SERVO: They're just shooting
caps off on a post card.
Squibs.
CROW: Well, shall we go
in the conference room,
where it's quieter?
This is awful.
How do you like
them guys?
...San Francisco yet.
They never got bombed
in the last war.
You never got it, brother.
-I was in Guadal...
-MIKE: Oh, excuse me.
Mind if I get a cigarette?
Have a cigar.
Oh, thanks.
-MIKE: Better.
-Anybody got a light?
CROW: I think I hear one coming.
[ Explosion ]
What's the chance of hiring your
cab to drive me there and go...?
SERVO: Come on,
would you light my cigar?
Good luck.
SERVO: Stop it!
You know, it's funny the world
is coming to an end,
but you and I are sitting here
having dinner?
SERVO: Funny ha-ha or?
Boy, I was hungry.
I know what you mean.
CROW: Yeah,
you ate all my food, you pig.
Every once in a while, I forget
what's happening in the world.
-SERVO: I'm just dumb.
-And feel good.
MIKE: I have valium blackouts.
As if I just met a new beau.
-You have.
-SERVO: Enjoy my headshot.
One I like very much.
He likes you even more.
CROW: Taster's Choice,
the final chapter.
-SERVO: Yeah.
-War or no war,
people have to eat and drink.
MIKE: Still got to use
the crapper.
Or make love.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do...
There have been
no further reports
of bombing from the west coast.
But an unconfirmed
report maintains...
Gentlemen,
we just smashed his
largest A-bomb plant.
The next bomb, Oregon.
Our B-36 has reached target
at 2300.
CROW: It was closed.
They blew a hole
right through the middle
of his plant.
How many workers there?
MAN: About 50,000.
How many casualties
would you estimate there?
-SERVO: Oh, a lot.
-...say at least half of them.
Well, what will happen
if he hits New York, Chicago,
the way we hit him?
CROW: Can't you just be happy?
It'd be tough.
MIKE: Your son drew
another giraffe, sir.
He's landed paratroops
in California.
The enemy is dropping
parachute troops
on the outskirts of the city.
The Army needs these tanks.
We got to get on them,
repair them, and do them fast.
What about the tractors
on the production line?
Oh, get them out of the road,
dump them in the bay, anything.
Let me emphasize
that it's touch and go
whether we can hold the city.
A dozen tanks one way or another
can make all the difference.
We'll get them ready fast.
Tell the men they're on a
24-hour shift
until those tanks are repaired.
A 24-hour shift for what?
To make more money for you?
We don't have to work
for this rat anymore.
He's finished.
All the capitalist rats
are finished.
Why don't you drop dead?
Why does he want to make tanks?
SERVO: Rick, save me.
When he could make
more money building tractors,
he build tractors.
SERVO: What are you,
County-- oh, wow.
Up, up with hands-- up.
SERVO: Tractor Police,
John Deere Squad.
Ah, you are here.
Just in time.
I'm in charge here now.
-SERVO: Aye.
-You were right.
Your men will work
a 24-hour shift
until the tanks are repaired,
but it is the people's army
who will use them.
[ Gunshots ]
SERVO: This is
for Alice Chalmers.
Take on the job,
you will get your order.
CROW: Hi, I miss anything?
-SERVO: Oh, whoop.
-Ooh.
CROW: Let me get two
15-minute break-- oh.
When middle managers rebel.
SERVO: Ugh.
Gonna need a new shift super.
Why do people like you always
think you can beat anybody
with your bare hands?
MIKE:
That's an interesting question.
-And I think to...
-I have my life to live for...
You would build tanks
in this factory.
CROW:
Don't finish sentences for me.
You still have time.
Only you will build them for us.
-That's what you think.
-Shut up.
CROW:
I just wanna build tractors.
[ Crying ]
But my orders
are to keep you alive.
MIKE: So are you gonna finish
the windows?
We need this factory, you see.
And you know how to run it
better than anybody else.
So, there is only one
thing to do.
You are so dead right.
SERVO: Little man,
I think I love you.
I'm just a man who can do it.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Oh.
[ Gunshots ]
[ Screams ]
MIKE: Boy, he almost made it.
CROW: Okay, I'm dead.
Fine.
Killer day at the office.
San Francisco fell
at 12:00 today,
and the invaders have
established a firm foothold
on American soil.
Our military air bases
within fighter plane range
of Northern California have
been knocked out by A-bombs.
MIKE:
That's my boyfriend you know.
...that the Army is being
withdrawn to a defense line
along the Western borders
of the Rocky Mountains.
SERVO: Knock it off over there!
CROW: Ding.
We now switch controls
to Washington, D.C.
for an official message.
CROW: [ Laughing ]
Hi, kids.
[ Laughing ]
SERVO: Oh.
MAN: Despite a heroic effort
by our Armed Forces...
SERVO: Bozo has been cancelled.
MAN: ...the enemy invaders
have now secured San Francisco,
Oakland,
Astoria, Oregon,
-and Port Townsend.
-CROW: And Cucamonga.
MAN: To the people of these
cities I bring this message.
SERVO: You're on your own.
MAN: Do not despair.
CROW: For those of you
not flash-fried.
MAN: At 10:00 this morning,
England and France
declared war on our side.
SERVO: France has pledge crêpes.
MAN: All the nations
included in the Atlantic pact
have risen to defend
the free world.
CROW:
With strongly worded cables,
they're very put out.
MAN: Despite the unprovoked
nature of the attack,
the war has not been
as one-sided
as it may now seem to you.
SERVO: I will now read
The Velveteen Rabbit.
MAN: For every atom bomb
dropped on our country,
we have taken three
to the enemy's heartland.
SERVO: Whoo.
MAN: And we have huge stocks
of atomic weapons in reserve.
CROW: Everything must go.
MAN: Stocks large enough
to eventually crush the enemy
on his native soil.
MIKE: He's always bragging
about his huge stocks.
MAN: And end forever his power
to make war
on any nation anywhere.
So be of good courage.
SERVO: I think Peggy Noonan
wrote the speech.
MAN: For we have met
the first shock of aggression,
and we have returned
blow for blow.
CROW: And that boy's name
was Raymond Burr.
MAN: And even as I
speak to you,
CROW: I'm not wearing pants.
MAN: our Pacific fleet
is carrying the conflict
to the enemy's homeland.
SERVO: But first,
victory at sea.
[ Cannon fire ]
Excuse me, are you
the enemy's homeland?
[ Cannon fire continues ]
MIKE: We're destroying
their beach resorts
and vacation areas.
CROW: Another senseless
fly-by shooting.
SERVO: The Dean Martin-
Jerry Lewis feud is heating up.
I wish they'd go back
to that president's speech.
That was a lot more fascinating.
CROW:
Yeah, that was great.
SERVO: Remember
that president's speech?
CROW: Oh, how can I forget?
Loved it.
[ Gunshots ]
SERVO: Oh, not Levittown, no!
-MIKE: Not the hog barn!
-SERVO: Please.
[ Gunshots ]
CROW:
They bomb our nation's hobos.
SERVO: They took out
Boxcar Willie.
[ Gunfire, explosion ]
Ooh.
MIKE: Come on, aren't they
overreacting just a bit?
SERVO: I think someone's
heated up here.
CROW: The Carnival Cruise Line
fights back.
♪ If you could see me die. ♪
SERVO: Wait, these many bombs?
Must be a comedy club.
ALL: [ Laughs ]
MIKE: Do they have to follow
the freeway when they're flying?
SERVO: I guess.
CROW: The freeway
to the danger zone.
So, World War III is gonna be
a lot like World War II.
-SERVO: Looks like.
-MIKE: Mm-hmm.
CROW: Similar design.
SERVO: Ratatat-tat.
Ratatat-tat.
MIKE: No, I can't swim.
I have tubes in my ears.
SERVO: Hey.
I'm fine, just a little dizzy.
No problem,
I've got it under control.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: And I'll just put
your arm back on.
MIKE: Mount Man.
-SERVO: [ Chuckles ]
-How do you feel?
I feel great.
How much of the red stuff
did you take out?
Just a pint.
The next time
I'll give you a fifth.
All right, come around
in about 12 weeks.
CROW: I only hear that joke
about eight million times a day.
MAN: Hi, honey.
FEMALE: Hey,
what are you doing here?
Oh, I thought I'd spare you
a few red corpuscles.
-Swell.
-SERVO: War's been a boon
to this guy.
Tried to join
the Air Force today...
CROW: Tried to join as a WAC.
Ninety thousand guys
are trying to join now
that it's too late to train men.
What they need is equipment.
What we need is blood.
MIKE: Well, take all of his.
MAN: You sure you know
what you're doing, huh?
-CARLA: Please.
-SERVO: But now that you
mention it,
I do have no idea.
-It's cold.
-Don't be such a sissy.
CROW: Did you ever see
The World According to Garp?
SERVO: Ow, ow, oh.
-Make a fist.
-Okay.
-You know you're beautiful?
-CROW: Yes, I know.
We're ready.
Does she know what she's doing
with that thing?
-You can trust her.
-Yeah, I don't trust--
I trust you, I don't trust...
CROW: Because she had thing
and I was with the thing.
SERVO: [ Laughing ]
MIKE: He has no blood.
There's no blood in him.
He has...
CROW: Man, I really like cattle.
MAN: All over America,
long lines are forming
in front of
Red Cross Blood Bank
centers,
but authorities estimate
that another five million pints
are needed immediately.
Even more if they ramp up
bomb attacks
on the major centers
of population.
SERVO: Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean you look exactly
like Linda Hunt.
Gosh, it's sure great to talk
to my kids
from Boulder City.
Take the first turn
to the right.
Not far to go, huh?
We'll be home in 10 minutes.
You'll be home, brother, not me.
They got a new flag
over my home.
SERVO: Whoo.
That's too bad.
CROW: But just drive, okay?
Got any family
in San Francisco?
Just me and the cab.
I'll give the two of you
a job on my ranch.
Oh, thanks.
SERVO: And there's
an airport fee,
you know that, right?
Look at those bombers.
I'm sure glad
we've got a lot of them.
You said it.
SERVO: Mm-hmm.
Huh?
Jet bombers with
swept-back wings.
I got you.
We just intercepted a jet
attack headed this way.
They think maybe
the dam's a target.
How many planes?
How far away?
-I got you.
-SERVO: How far away?
Last seen at six C for Charlie.
-SERVO: You just talk to him.
-About a dozen jets,
120 miles west of here.
They about shot down
most of them.
SERVO: Oops,
stock footage at 3:00.
What's that?
CROW: Yeah, it's about a dozen
jets heading this way.
Oh, my God!
Post 327 to command,
post 327 to command,
enemy jets approaching,
Boulder Dam.
Enemy jets approaching
Enemy planes coming in.
Open fire.
SERVO: The Guns of Navarone
versus the Demonic Toys.
And Dollman is there.
CROW: Don't let them
get to the gift shop.
MIKE: If you shoot them down,
you just have to clean them up.
SERVO: This makes me pine
for Red Dawn.
CROW: Avenge me.
-Avenge me.
-Three jets attacking dam.
MIKE: I mean, darn, excuse me.
SERVO: Launch cargo.
MIKE: Just realized
the president's approval rating
must be plummeting.
CROW: How do I not dive anymore?
SERVO: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, those zooms are deadly.
Wow.
MIKE:
Vince Coleman's final revenge.
CROW: Despite the best efforts
of the little Dutch boy...
[ Explosion ]
Sounded like something
blew up.
MAN: Emergency announcement.
Enemy planes are attacking
Boulder Dam.
I repeat, enemy planes
are attacking Boulder Dam.
CROW: Good thing I brought
the motorman's helper.
MAN: The dam's...
MAN: Attention, all citizens,
Boulder Dam has been destroyed
by enemy actions.
Evacuate all low ground
immediately.
Attention, all citizens.
Step on it,
we got to get to my family.
MIKE: This guy's gonna be
so mad when he finds out
there's an express bus
he could've taken.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Sir,
you're up to about $11,000,
sure you don't want me
to drop you off?
Look at that.
SERVO: Gee, Central Casting
sent over a family.
Daddy!
MAN: The dam's out.
-WOMAN: The dam?
-MAN: Yes, they bombed it.
Boulder Dam.
Get in, quick, hurry.
MIKE: Oh, great to see you
too, honey.
♪ Up through the ground
came a-bubblin' crude ♪
♪ Water that is ♪
Water will be a hundred
feet deep here any minute.
What happened?
Those bombers that just flew
over, they weren't ours.
Can't you go any faster?
SERVO: Sure, I'd drive you here
from San Francisco,
but I guess I am a jerk, huh?
-Mommy, I'm scared.
-Shh, darling.
MIKE: Usually when there's a
flood, you can never find a cab.
Am I right here?
CROW: We should've got
a Checker cab.
SERVO: [ Humming ]
-Hank, oh.
-Faster, faster.
SERVO: Oh, guess the water
knew a shortcut, huh?
[ Screaming ]
-SERVO: Oh.
-MIKE: I knew I'd get soaked
for this cab ride.
SERVO: The meter
is still running, pal.
Oh, ironically he always used
to leave his hat in cabs.
CROW: Hmm, sad.
-MIKE: Oh, look at this.
-SERVO: Oh, my God.
MIKE: Boy, when
that doll wets...
[ Chuckles ]
Destruction of Boulder Dam
by an atomic missile today
was only the culminating
disaster in what will go down
in history as Black Friday
for the United States
of America.
CROW: Or freaky Friday.
MAN: At 10:27 this morning,
off the coast of California,
an American warship
was the victim
of another new atomic weapon,
when the carrier Crown Point
suffered a direct hit
by an atomic torpedo,
first victim of a weapon
that threatens
the very existence
of the United States fleet.
The Crown Point waged
a gallant fight for survival
but at 5:20 this afternoon,
the fire reached
her boiler room,
and Capt. Headley gave
the order to abandon ship.
SERVO: Wise decision, captain.
MIKE: We told Dom DeLuise
to stand in the middle,
but I blame this on Exxon.
Meanwhile,
flames swept the entire
State of California tonight,
as the people
of the Pacific Coast
put their industrial
establishments
to the torch,
rather than allow them
to fall into enemy hands.
SERVO: Oh.
MAN: Here is a food
warehouse in Oakland...
MIKE: The chicken's done.
MAN: ...its owners to keep
the thousands of tons of flour
and sugar it held from being
used to feed the enemy.
-SERVO: War and peace.
-MAN: This is Richmond,
California,
land of western petroleum.
-CROW: No, it's not.
-MAN: A million gallons
of high-test airplane gasoline
go up in flames
to implement
the Scorched Earth policy
with which a resolute
civilian population
is meeting the first invasion
of America
since the War of 1812.
MIKE: When was that war?
MAN: Disaster follows disaster
as railroad employees
wreck their own trains
to slow the enemy drive.
SERVO: Pretty dumb, huh?
MAN: A steel plant
built at a cost
of $50 million dollars
burns to the ground.
CROW: And Allstate is there.
One part of the
terrible financial
balance sheet of war.
Billions of dollars
of property lost
to the American people forever
because we did not provide
a strong enough army
to protect ourselves.
SERVO: Aw.
I heard they got 10,000
transport planes
flying in soldiers.
Probably got half a million
men in California by now.
-SERVO: Well, the...
-Fella I know said his brother
heard he had better
than 60 ships
-in the San Francisco Harbor.
-SERVO: You see the problem...
They landed a couple
of hundred heavy tanks
and maybe a thousand
atom bombs.
The way I figure it's this:
They know they can't
fight all the way
across the United States.
You know, this landing's
just a diversion, see?
I mean, they're just waiting
for us to send
our whole army out west.
Then they'll overrun Europe.
Jesus. That's what they're
after - airplane bases.
-SERVO: Can't talk to you, too.
-...get them, they'll start
to bomb Pittsburgh, Detroit,
places like that.
And we sure bombed the daylights
out of them yesterday.
Oh, another drink, Tim.
-CROW: Sure, Mr. Hot.
-Coming right up.
How about letting me
buy you one?
MIKE: You come
to this war often?
No, thanks.
Might as well have another.
You know what the fellow says,
"Drink and be merry,
for tomorrow we die."
CROW: Not that funny
when it's true, Ed.
I'd rather not, thanks.
MIKE: I need more woman friends.
Well, this war has really put
a spring in my step.
-Hi, honey.
-Hi.
-How's the blood bank?
-It's fine.
And we've got a new record
this week.
You set a record with me
a long time ago.
MIKE: God, I'm smooth.
Anyway...
Give me a beer, Tim, huh?
Well, they turned me down
again today.
The Air Force?
Navy this time.
Air Force doesn't want me,
army doesn't want me,
Navy doesn't want me.
CROW: Apparently,
I'm too good-looking.
That's the best thing
I've heard today.
I mean it, too.
SERVO: You're a Hindu.
Why wouldn't the Navy take you?
-Same old story.
-CROW: They're jealous.
More men than
they have weapons for.
Soldier is no good without a gun
and a sailor is no good
without a ship.
Don't let it get you down, chum.
Remember old Tim's motto.
Let Jack do it.
-Jack?
-CROW: What the hell?
TIM: George's brother.
MIKE: Well, the whole George
thing just isn't that funny.
Oh, you're killing me.
CROW: You set a record with my--
oh, yeah, used that, hmm?
-Right now?
-Right now.
I'm with you.
CROW: And I'll be back
for you later, Timmy.
TIM: Hey, Vince.
You forgot your beer.
-You drink it.
-SERVO: I don't drink this
-swill...
-Yeah.
[ Glugs ]
[ Laughs ]
MIKE: He's got cirrhosis
of the liver.
Tim, you're a character.
What are you gonna do now
that there's a war on?
Same thing I did
in the last couple of wars.
Shake daiquiris.
SERVO: I'm a patriot.
CROW: You should do comedy.
You're just so funny.
[ Laughs ]
MAN:
Emergency announcement.
-SERVO: Hmm?
-Radar screens have picked up
unidentified aircraft
approaching New York.
-SERVO: Radar.
-The red alert is on.
I repeat,
emergency announcement.
Unidentified planes
approaching New York.
The red alert is on.
CROW: Patty's in trouble again.
You suppose they're really
going to bomb New York?
They threatened to.
It was on the newswire.
We didn't wanna release it
and start a panic.
SERVO: We thought it would
make a nice surprise.
I'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid at all.
SERVO: Neither am I, let's go.
-MIKE: Yeah.
-CROW: This is our war.
Carla, there may not be
much time left,
but in the few days there are,
I want to spend it with you.
I want that, too.
[ Doors closing ]
-I am Mr. Jenga.
-Jenga, Jenga, Jenga.
-Hey, I win again.
-Hey.
SERVO: What's so hard
about this game, anyway?
MIKE: Servo,
that's not the point.
SERVO: Then, what is the point?
[ Indistinct chatter ]
BOMB: Hey, hiya.
-Hi.
-Hey, Mike.
It looks like some kind of bomb.
Some kind of bomb?
I'm the bomb, kid!
I'm it, Mr. A1-Armageddon-
Duck-and-Cover-end-of-the-world-
flesh-melting-atom-bomb.
Wow.
But you can call me Bomb.
MIKE: Why so glum, Bomb?
You're looking
at a dinosaur, kid.
I could remember the salad days,
lounging in the belly
of the B-52,
cruising up and down
the coast of Yakutsk.
I meant something, then.
Hey, Lenny,
how about another
Manhattan project,
put it on my tab?
You probably don't even remember
the Cuban missile crisis.
MIKE: Well, I, you know...
Let me tell you something.
Bombs don't kill people.
Well, I guess maybe they do,
but the point is,
I can be used
for good things, too.
You want a big stinking hole
in the ground?
I'm your man.
Should you really be smoking?
Oh, the crap I take from these
sandal-wearing burnouts.
You can't help a kid
with nuclear arms.
Oh, yeah.
What do you call these, huh?
Oh,
I better mellow out.
Core temperature
is starting to heat up.
Yeah.
Well, I feel kind of funny.
I-- boom.
[ Screams ]
I'm just kidding, guys.
-Oh, be careful.
-Geez.
It can't be that bad, Mr. Bomb.
Things are looking up.
Take North Korea, for instance.
Oh, yeah, the instability
in Eastern Europe.
-Yeah.
-There's always a despotic
dictator or two looking
for Mr. Good Bomb.
-Sure.
-Yeah.
That's right.
You got a point there, you know?
I guess things
ain't so bad, after all.
Yeah, I feel better already.
-Thanks, guys.
-Yeah. sure.
I think I'll go call
that weasel Helen Caldicott up
I like to breathe real heavy
and then hang up.
She knows.
[ Laughs ]
Hey, thanks again.
See you.
-Okay, no problem.
-Bye.
[ Laughs ]
-Oh, sweet guy, huh?
-Yeah.
I'm sure glad
we could cheer him up.
-Yeah.
-Say, Mike,
did we just do something
horribly wrong?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Oh.
-Oh, boy.
-Oh, we'll be right back.
-I hope.
-Yeah.
[ Music playing ]
-SERVO: Lovely bomb, huh.
-CROW: Mm-hmm.
New York's really gone downhill.
MIKE: I guarantee you one thing.
The cockroaches will be okay.
CROW: Yeah.
SERVO: I wanna burn up
in a city that never sleeps.
CROW: This is all
Andrew Giuliani's fault.
SERVO: Okay, London is burning,
but what about New York?
CROW: Try getting a cab now.
SERVO: At least there's
no school tomorrow.
MIKE: Oh, Sid and Nancy
stayed there.
-SERVO: The Chelsea Hotel.
-CROW: Irwin Allen's
Straight
Out Of Brooklyn.
SERVO: I'd loot,
but what would I get?
[ Chuckles ]
MIKE: At least everyone
who lived through the blitz
can rest assured
it's been immortalized
as filler for this movie.
CROW: Barney Rubble.
MIKE: God,
I must've been fantastic.
Oh, no.
No, are we late for happy hour?
Hi, perhaps you recognize me.
I'm a very popular radio
and TV personality.
CROW: My daiquiri!
-Is he okay?
-He's dead.
SERVO: Even in death, he amuses.
Carla.
MIKE: Our bartender died.
CROW: Thank God.
For a minute I thought this war
was gonna affect me personally.
[ Crying ]
MIKE: So, this is the elevator?
[ Screams ]
First estimates indicate
that more than 30,000 dead
with the victims of the
A-bombing of New York City,
when an enemy plane
pierced our defenses
and dropped its deadly cargo
late last night.
-CROW: Sufferin' succotash.
-Along with the heavy steel
and concrete construction
of city skyscrapers
held down the death toll
as more than 50,000 injured
filled New York hospitals alone.
-MIKE: What hospitals?
-City and state civilian
defense workers
are on a 24-hour shift,
and aid is pouring
into New York City
from every direction.
-MIKE: Or into London.
-Any further report
on the New York attack?
Here are some air pictures
of the damage.
About a third of the city
has been quarantined.
-Radiation.
-SERVO: Lot of owies and stuff.
How did the radiation casualties
compare with the direct
fatalities?
-MIKE: Really good.
-No report on that yet.
What's his purpose?
Why should he capture one
small part of the Pacific Coast
and then stop?
He may be stockpiling A-bombs
to hit our industrial centers,
in which case, this may have
been a probing attack
to test our defenses.
CROW: Don't say probing, sir.
Today, we made
the critical attack.
SERVO: It's a spebs... meeting.
Every man, speak English,
every man, wear
United States uniform.
SERVO: And we will dress
like village people.
Our six generals are dead.
All government officers
killed these people today.
All soldiers--
what is the word for...?
-SERVO: Linguine, sir.
-Soldier.
Oh, yeah.
Infilter.
Our soldiers infilter
and assassinate.
No one likes to give order.
No command for the army.
No leader for the government.
Ezra Pound wrote that.
The bombing of New York
be a diversion?
CROW: From what?
To keep our all air strength
away from the West.
CROW: Oh.
Or it could be,
perhaps, that's what
he wants us to think.
-SERVO: Oh, he's a knob.
-Perhaps he'd like us to send
everything west and leave
the East Coast unprotected.
I don't believe we've seen
his main attack yet.
Put the red alert on everywhere.
-CROW: I get to do it.
-MIKE: No, I'll do it.
-CROW: No, I'm doing it.
-MIKE: You fend their attacks.
SERVO: Size-14 navy pants,
and your next item, please?
CROW: Take out wrenched ankle.
Ha, ha.
MIKE: Hmm.
I hate it when wars are rerun.
SERVO: Happy birthday,
Plain States.
CROW: I wonder
what they are doing.
SERVO: Despite the war,
meaningless activities continue.
Meanwhile, at Milton Bradley...
CROW: I'm putting an end
to this right now.
MAN: One unidentified craft,
Section Charlie, zone four.
Looks like a transport.
Yes, that's the third.
Better go after it.
MAN: Group three,
rendezvous at Section Baker.
Get going, fellas.
MIKE: Put out your cigarettes.
Uh-oh.
No, don't go out there.
No, I sense stock footage.
CROW: Oh, boy.
I'm flossing my hinder,
even as I fly.
SERVO: I like the way
my outfit feels.
MIKE: These Boy Scout
overnights are getting intense.
CROW: Excuse me, Steve,
I believe this is my
flight pattern.
Thank you very much.
MIKE: Oh, pardon me.
We picked up three unidentified
transport planes.
Big boys.
That's the Joker.
One south, one east,
and one north.
You sent out interceptors?
-After all three.
-CROW: I'm rankishly handsome.
-You don't suppose...
-There have been no reports
from the west, sir.
Ring post 21.
-Yes, sir.
-SERVO: So I've seen catholic
school clothing drives
better organized than this.
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Whistling ]
CROW: You wanna get that?
SERVO: No, you?
CROW: Just let it ring.
SERVO: God, I'm beat. Man,
what a day.
-Oh.
-ARTHUR: And so,
in this critical hour...
CROW: Let's make cookies.
...I call upon the Congress
of the United States
to back its military leaders
-with the last dollar.
-MIKE: Oh, no, Grand Funk.
-Whoo!
-The last man-hour of labor.
MIKE: You're not funny.
ARTHUR: The last American life.
-CROW: No.
-SERVO: No.
MIKE: Stock footage.
SERVO: Empire of the Sun
didn't have as many planes.
CROW: We never talk anymore.
SERVO: Okay, hang on.
We're-- Russians, right?
Or are we Americans
dressed as Russians?
I'm confused.
MIKE: You guys
want your parachutes?
CROW: Oh.
Is this biblical, like a plague
of Russian covers the Earth,
something like that?
MIKE: Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
SERVO: Pardon me one second.
CROW: Excuse me, Ivan.
MIKE: Dmitri, I'm leaving next.
Thank you.
SERVO: This is what happens when
you parachute between 5:00
and 7:00 in the evening.
CROW: [ Yawns ]
...parachuting.
MIKE: Yeah, that's pretty much.
SERVO: The McLaughlin Group
from the skies.
CROW: I ask you,
Morton Kondracke...
SERVO: One of these parachutes
was washed in Tide,
the others weren't.
CROW: Ah, the sandy beaches
of Dupont Circle.
MIKE: This plane comes
with a convenient handle
so it totes easily.
Call now.
CROW: Heck of a luge run.
SERVO: Oh, no.
They're hitting us
with Don "The Snake" Prudhomme.
Whew.
CROW:
Obsessive-compulsive skydiver.
Oh, four of my chutes
didn't open.
Oh, I'm okay.
MIKE: The Piano Part 2,
-Where Pianos Dare.
-SERVO: Where pianos dare.
CROW: So, what part
of Washington D.C. is this?
MAN: Where's the Capitol?
Hello? Hello?
Yes, sir.
Outpost 26
calling general headquarters
-priority line.
-CROW: Grand Hotel.
Hello?
They've landed where?
SERVO: My patio?
That's going too far.
Across the Potomac
in American uniforms?
Standby for...
SERVO: Potomac, what's that?
Double the companies guarding
the White House, the Capitol,
the senate building
and the House.
Yes, sir.
And have them
challenge everybody
no matter what uniform.
MIKE: Challenge some people.
-Challenge almost all people.
-Halt.
Who goes there?
Company B, 183rd Infantry.
183rd, that's an Illinois
outfit, ain't it?
Yes, yes.
-Chicago, Illinois.
-MIKE: Do you know Bob?
Did you ever go see
the Cubs play?
SERVO: Yeah, they won.
Oh, damn, no.
Cubs?
A cub is a young animal, a bear.
Sergeant of the guards!
CROW: No, no, no.
Ooh.
Halt, who goes there?
CROW: The Cubs, that's turtles--
Oh, never mind.
ARTHUR: If we as members
of Congress
have ever been lacking in vigor
in our nation's defense...
SERVO: Bring on the strippers.
...if we have ever failed
to realize
the urgency
of the nation's peril...
MIKE: Well, then, sorry.
...let us be
doubly vigilant now.
Let us set an example
of fighting Americanism...
CROW: We got to get him off,
we're losing the crowd.
-SERVO: Zoinks.
-ARTHUR: Let us continue to...
CROW: I call shut up.
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
the enemy is attempting
to seize the seat of government!
We are surrounded!
CROW: One more song,
and then we got to go.
Hide your prostitutes.
[ Music playing ]
Do you remember
what Senator Baker said
when the Military
Appropriations Bill
came up for vote?
He said we could safely reduce
our armed forces
by half.
He wasn't only wrong, he's dead.
MIKE: Guess he won't do
that again.
CROW: Sorry, Bob,
they're out of pineapple.
Enemy demands surrender
of my state
or threatens to atom bomb
our principal cities.
Can you protect me?
Signed, Gov. Clayton.
Can you?
SERVO: Tell him yes,
then postdate the letter.
How do we stand?
We're driving him
out of the city.
In another 24 hours,
the government will be safe.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
they've invaded New York.
ALL: New York City?
...the window here at our
improvised radio transmitter.
SERVO: I'm so admirable,
you know.
I saw hundreds of enemy troops
moving in the streets below.
MIKE:
He's speaking into his Emmy.
...before they find us and take
this station off the air.
Vince, they're coming
into the building now.
In the little time we have left,
I wanna tell you how proud
you can be of the ordinary
citizens of New York.
It seems every man
and boy today has become
a guerilla fighter.
I saw taxi drivers use
their cabs as weapons,
to mow down enemy troops.
I saw high school boys
attack enemy tanks
with pop bottles
full of gasoline.
I saw modern policemen
become a fighting...
MAN: We take over now.
-[ Gunshot ]
-Oh, Vince.
SERVO: That was
the Mercury Players
presenting Invasion USA.
MAN: The people's
government of America
will take the wealth
from the greedy,
the speculators,
and the capitalistic
bourgeoisie.
CROW: Yakov Smirnoff, no.
MAN: ...workers whose labor
will never again be exploited
for the benefit
of the warmongers --
SERVO: They love their country.
The people's government brings
the citizens of New York...
-CROW: Fudge.
-...a new freedom.
-CROW: Oh.
-A freedom based on order.
A freedom based on loyalty
to the leaders of the party,
your party,
which will work hand-in-hand
with the Marxist
Democratic leadership
of all other nations,
so that never again
will war be necessary
among the civilized peoples
of the world.
MIKE: Well, that guy
makes a lot of sense, too.
I'm torn between mourning
my boyfriend and subscribing
to Marxist dogma.
Hmm, mourn boyfriend,
Marxist dogma, hmm.
[ Music playing ]
[ Knocking on door ]
SERVO: Hmm?
CROW: Hmm?
Red Army cable, open up.
SERVO: I am your personal
Stalin representative.
Please step aside.
Is this your boyfriend?
-Vince.
-SERVO: Oh, I guess he wasn't
thinking when he asked
to swing by
his girlfriend's place.
-MIKE: Mm-hmm.
-They're saving me to broadcast
the glories of the new order.
CROW: Norton?
You're not going
to broadcast for them.
What do you think?
Hey, buster, do you mind
if we sit down?
All right.
Sit down.
SERVO: You got any shoe polish?
I wanna spread it on bread
and drink the alcohol.
Look.
Look, you guys, don't you
drink whiskey, good whiskey?
I drink it myself over there.
Ah, whiskey, whiskey good.
Da.
-Yeah.
-You try trick, I kill you.
Your woman, too.
No tricks, no tricks.
CROW: Geez,
just because you're invading
doesn't mean you have to be
such a jerk, Ivan.
Good whiskey.
SERVO: I didn't realize
the Russian Army
would have chaperones.
MIKE: But the Communist
to citizen ratio is remarkable.
...I'm gonna get you out.
You don't know
how wonderful it is
just to see your face,
to know that you're alive.
I never thought
I'd see you again, either.
CROW: I'd never thought
I'd see you alive again first.
Vince, if we could
just stay together.
We should've met
another time, honey,
a year ago, a month.
SERVO: Look, you're getting
on that Russian.
A month ago, I wanted
a mink stole.
I thought it was important.
SERVO: That touches
my huge heart.
CROW: You got Eagle snack,
maybe dip or something?
Vince, if I had my life
to live over again...
That's what everybody's
saying, honey.
MAN: You drink whiskey, too.
Please, no.
She doesn't want any.
-CROW: What the?
-Drink.
-CROW: [ Gasps ]
-Listen, honey, I...
[ Gunshot ]
CROW: Honey, oh,
why didn't you just drink
the whiskey?
MIKE: There, some Miller time.
Get out.
Get out of here.
He is dead.
Now you my woman.
MIKE: So being romanced
by Mr. French.
CROW: Hey, hey,
"nyet" means "nyet".
No.
CROW: Oh, right in one
of his many soft spots.
-MIKE: Wow.
-CROW: This has happened
so many times to that guy.
MIKE: It can't be good
for his self-esteem.
CROW: Dorothy.
Dorothy.
SERVO: Bartender, what's this
woman doing in my drink?
MIKE: What the--
it's a dream or some...
CROW: What?
You didn't know that?
-MIKE: No.
-SERVO: What a knob.
-CROW: [ Laughs ]
-SERVO: Okay, folks.
Drink up.
Hallucination's over.
CROW: This is very
Jacob's Ladder-esque.
SERVO: This happens
every Thursday.
[ Imitates chicken sound ]
CROW: Everything's normal,
except their pants are missing.
Did I just-- because you were...
You're alive.
Hey.
Didn't we fly
to the West Coast together?
SERVO: No, shh, we didn't.
No, we didn't, we didn't.
Yes, but what are we doing
back here?
We are in New York, aren't we?
Are you kidding?
The man that was sitting
behind that brandy glass,
where is he?
Ohman?
Well, I guess he left.
CROW: He works for
the Psychic Friends Network.
Hey, he went out
without paying for his drink.
You know who he is?
Well, yeah, he's some kind
of a fortune teller,
hypnotizes people,
he says.
MIKE: It's supposed to be
good for you.
Shows them
what's gonna happen.
A phony if I ever saw one.
-OHMAN: Am I, Tim?
-SERVO: Dude, I mean,
phony in the good sense.
CROW: Hello, everyone.
You know, you only rent cognac.
SERVO: [ Gulping ]
CROW: No, he swallowed the girl.
That's for the drink.
You asked for me, congressman?
Did you enjoy your little
excursion into the future?
SERVO: Yeah, put this somewhere.
Thank you.
Mass hypnotism.
That's what it was.
-Yeah, exactly.
-Yes.
Then, all that stuff about
the enemy taking over my plant,
it isn't on the level, is it?
It isn't really gonna happen?
It is, unless you do
something to stop it.
SERVO: You have to give
to public television.
Tomorrow springs
from today like...
SERVO: Uhh, something.
...like water from a rock.
If you want to change
what you will become...
SERVO: Give me a buzz.
...first change what you are.
That goes for everybody.
Good day, everybody.
CROW: Enigmatic bastard,
isn't he?
MIKE: Mm-hmm.
Well, I guess I better be going.
Maybe I'll make some
of those tank parts.
I'll be going with you
as far as Washington.
I've got some things to do also.
Well, I'm in on this, too.
So long, Tim.
TIM: So long, fellas.
Come back again.
Finished with your drink?
-Yes, but...
-I'll take care of her.
Is that the way you want it?
MIKE: Vince and I are gonna make
our own tank parts.
Okay, good luck
to the both of you.
CROW: You know,
I think hypno-dating
is the wave of the future.
-SERVO: Hmm.
-I guess it's my turn.
Do you happen to know
the address
of the nearest blood bank?
SERVO: 1300 Me Avenue.
-I'll show you the way.
-SERVO: Wow.
MIKE: So now they have
a whole history together.
-SERVO: History.
-CROW: Would you mind
putting on that nurse's
outfit again?
SERVO: Would you really jump
out a window for me, you nut?
MIKE: I mean,
would you right now?
[ Laughing ]
MAN: Father of our country,
George Washington said...
MIKE: Hi, I'm George Washington.
MAN: To be prepared for war
is one of the most
effectual means
-of preserving peace.
-CROW: So why the portrait
of Terence Trent D'Arby?
[ Music playing ]
[ Doors closing ]
Fellas, this movie
has completely changed me.
Mike, Crow, think of it.
I mean, this existence
is nothing but some grand
hypnotic trance created by
some depraved Svengoolie.
I mean, at any time,
we're all gonna wake up
to our own true reality.
Our true reality
is that you're nuttier
than a fruitcake.
I truly believe
this is all a dream.
Uh-huh, and you're
completely convinced?
Mike, honey, I am so sure
that this is a dream.
I want you to hit me.
No, no.
-I'm not gonna hit you.
-Please, I insist.
Now get that clown hammer.
No, I can't hit you.
I'm not asking you,
I'm telling you.
Get the clown hammer.
-Hit me.
-Okay, pal.
-This one?
-No, no, no.
The big one.
-Come on.
-All right.
-I mean it, come on.
-This one?
Yeah, yeah, that's the one.
Now, have at me, swing away.
But I can't hit you.
-Come on.
-You're my friend.
Have at me.
Okay, fine. I-- but what if this
isn't a dream, though?
Oh, but it is, my friend.
-It is.
-Hit him, hit him.
I am dream warrior.
Hit me.
-Send me. It won't do a thing.
-Step aside.
It's a dream.
It's all a dream.
-Here we go.
-I love dreaming.
Here we go.
-This is no dream at all.
-Hit me.
-Whoa.
-Oh, oh.
[ Screaming ]
Oh, well.
Hmm.
Letters?
Yeah, letters.
Good idea.
Why not?
Oh. Oh, my back hurts.
-Oh.
-Okay.
Well, we'll read this
first one here
from Alicia Evans and...
Hi, Alicia.
...put the text
on still store there.
-Yeah.
-She just has a nice letter.
She says hi
and how is everything
on the Satellite of Love.
-Good.
-Okay.
You're not missing much
on Earth.
-Oh, good.
-That makes me feel better.
I like when you guys
do skits or sing
or just talk to each other
every half hour.
Those are my favorite parts
of the show.
-Uh-huh.
-I like to draw pictures
of when you guys
do stuff like that.
-And then she includes some...
-Pictures.
-Ooh.
-Very colorful pictures...
-Those are nice.
-Oh, we'll skip that one.
That's nice.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Back up there.
Hey, what's that one?
This one says,
"Mike in his sailor suit."
CROW: Very nice.
I like the...
Rugged, huh?
Well, not really.
-All right.
-Definitely home on leave.
And then the last one
is a picture of us all
and put that up there
and it says,
"Gypsy sings well,"
which, you know, I don't know.
"Crow had a really cool hat on."
-I had a hat.
-He probably did.
Mike has a smile--
always has a smile...
-Aw, that's sweet.
-...that's forced onto my face.
And Tom is the smartest
of the robots.
-Well...
-Not anymore, huh?
No.
-Ooh!
-Claude?
-Funny.
-Vivian?
I'm almost convinced
that this isn't an illusion.
I'm gonna go lie down now.
Oh, oh.
Well, what do you think
you guys?
Is this all an illusion?
Hmm?
-You okay?
-SERVO: No.
-Oh.
-Is life an illusion.
In your dreams!
Geez.
Do you believe
these guys, Frank?
Talk about gullible.
Frank?
Who won the World Series?
I did.
Oh, okay.
Frank, why don't you check
out that guy, hmm?
Halt, who goes there?
Who won the World Series?
Well, until next time,
collective doofuses.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Music playing ]
Extra, paper,
America invaded. Read all about it!